// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Fill in the blank by meaningful word \"I ______ a rat.\" ",
    answer: "saw",
    options: [
      "black",
      "she",
      "saw",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Make meaningful word from given letters \"U\", \"R\", \"N\" ",
    answer: "RUN",
    options: [
      "URN",
      "RUN",
      "UR",
      "NRU"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Choose meaningless word from given options",
    answer: "azl",
    options: [
      "met",
      "pan",
      "top",
      "azl"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Make meaningful word from given letters \"S\", \"U\", \"B\"",
    answer: "BUS",
    options: [
      "SSB",
      "BUS",
      "BSS",
      "UUS"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Make meaningful word from given letters \"O\", \"N\", \"G\", \"A\", \"M\" ",
    answer: "MANGO",
    options: [
      "MANGO",
      "ANMGO",
      "GOANM",
      "ONGAM"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "choose correct word ",
    answer: "jump",
    options: [
      "lett",
      "mofx",
      "rdsa",
      "jump"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "which word is wrong ",
    answer: "ordq",
    options: [
      "text",
      "ordq",
      "find",
      "part"
    ]
  }
  /*
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Select correct Uppercase letter 'r' ",
    answer: "R",
    options: [
      "V",
      "R",
      "W",
      "A"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Find the letter 'C'",
    answer: "C",
    options: [
      "A",
      "Y",
      "C",
      "H"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Find the letter 'X'",
    answer: "X",
    options: [
      "V",
      "X",
      "A",
      "U"
    ]
  }
  */
];
